I am not the only traveler
Who is not repaid his debt?
I've been searching for a trail to follow
Again, take me back to the nightmare
Then that I can't tell myself
What the hell I'm supposed to do?
Not to ride alone with you
I head on and then I'll see you swimming down there
Take me back to the nightmare
I don't know what I'm supposed to do
You're crawling by the gusty
We'll be taking me back to the nightmare
When the night was full of terror
Then your eyes were filled with tears
When your head not touched me head
Take me back to the nightmare
I head on and then I'll see you swimming down there
I don't know what I'm supposed to do
I head on and then I'll see you
Take me back to the nightmare
I head on and then I'll see you swimming down there